

MUHAMMAD NAZAR ALAM

Jalan Bijaksana no 30, Cinere

Depok, Cinere, 16512 Jawa Barat

+6281517614380

nazaralam79@gmail.com



In Nazar Alam



Nazaralam.github.io

BIOGRAPHY

I am an ungraduate Computer science student with skills and enough experience in programming languages. Using Logical thinking and creative design skills and is now looking forward to take the on the next challenge in IT sector. Easily adaptation and high responsibility about my work.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Boost Buah by Putra Asih

Photographer | Aug 2019 - Present

As a Photographer and editor to make a content and publish it for a company(Putra_asih) in East Jakarta.

GENESIS CREATIVE STUDIO
 Photographer | Sept 2020 - Present
 As a freelance Photographer for graduation school



EDUCATION

UNGRADUATE

PRESIDENT UNIVERSITY (Majoring in IT)

SEPT 2018 - PRESENT GPA 3.32

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

- PIC DOCUMENTATION CompShadow 2019
- PIC DOCUMENTATION Comsphere 2020
- CHAIRPERSON Of SHUTTER PHOTOGRAPHY PRESIDENT UNIVERSITY 2020



PROJECTS

- WEBSITE PORTFOLIO PERSONAL (HTML, CSS, JS) //Nazaralam.github.io
- 3D Retangular Mirror Using Ray Tracing An Software to show the Ray Tracing on object using vb.net
- 3D Polygon Mesh
 An Software to draw Polygon Mesh in 3D using JAVA.
- Fine-Dining Information System Software for food ordering in restaurant using vb.net



SKILLS

Programming

- HTMLCSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- 07177100711
- Python
- PHP
- JAVA
- VISUAL BASIC
- C++
- MySQL

Additional Skills

- MS. Office
- Adobe Photoshop

COMPUTER

SCIENCE

INTEREST

Editing

Design UI/UX

Photography

RESPONSIBILITY

SOFT SKILLS

TEAMWORK

LEADERSHIP

ADAPTABLE

LANGUAGES

Native
English

Bahasa Indonesia

Intermediate

- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effect
- Adobe Lightroom
- Corel Draw
- 3D Vista Visual tour